你做到了
You did it.
我做到什么了
What did I do.
你开启了地狱之门
You opened the door.
莉莉丝就是最后一道封印
Lilith was the final seal.
我杀了她 我释放了路西法
I killed her, and I set Lucifer free.
还有嗜血的欲望吗 或者别的什么
Jonesing for another hit of bitch blood or what.
你就是米迦勒之剑
You're the michael sword.
- 你说我是剑是什么意思 - 你是米迦勒的武器
- What do you mean, I'm the sword - You're michael's weapon.
- 我是个皮囊 - 你就是皮囊
- I'm a vessel - You're the vessel.
鲁弗斯·特纳 他也是个猎人
Rufus Turner. He's a hunter.
你们最好祈祷还有命回来
I'm what you've got to look forward to if you survive.
这儿有重病号
Need some help here!
这是干什么
What the hell was that.
以诺派印记
An enochian sigil.
它能让任何天使都无法发现你们
It'll hide you from every angel.
包括路西法
in creation, including Lucifer.
艾伦 都是我的错
Ellen it was my fault.
乔没错
But Jo did good out there.
我理解你会这么生气
You're angry. I understand.
生气 生气根本毫无意义
Angry angry doesn't begin to touch it!
你是指我去猎杀魔鬼还是指别的
Is this about me hunting or something else.
你选择了恶魔而不是你的哥哥
You chose a demon over your own brother.
我不能再相信你了
I just don't think I can trust you.
他还是这样吗 都三天了
What's it been … like, three days now.
得让他振奋起来
We got to cheer him up.
或者给他来个背部推拿
Maybe I'll give him a back rub.
迪恩
Dean.
又怎么了
Well, what, then.
听着
Look.
我们要做好心理准备
We might have to wrap our heads around the idea.
鲍比这次可能难逃一难了
That Bobby might not just bounce back this time.
信封里是什么
What's in the envelope.
我胸部的X光片
Went to radiology.
象吃了外形诡异的枪子一样
Got some glamour shots.
这会让医生郁闷死
Let's just say the doctors are baffled.
什么鬼东西
Holy crap.
正好 卡西也给你刻了一套
Yeah, well, Cass carved you one, too.
喂
Hello.
卡西迪奥
Castiel.
说一下恶魔的事
Speak of the devil.
我在圣马丁医院
Uh St. Martin's hospital.
怎么了 什么事
Why. What are you …
卡西
Cass.
还真用上手机了 卡西
Cellphone, Cass really.
什么时候天使开始要与凡人联系了
Since when do angels need to reach out and touch someone.
所有的天使现在都找不到你们了 所有的
You're hidden from angels now … all angels.
我还不能…
I won't be able to simply …
前戏该够了吧
Enough foreplay.
过来开门见山 有话直说
Get over here and lay your damn hands on.
快点把我治好
Get healing … now.
我不行
I can't.
再说一遍
Say again.
我被赶出了天堂 天堂之力被废了很多
I'm cut off from heaven and much of heaven's power.
我不再无所不能了
Certain things, I can do. Certain things, I can't.
你是说在我可能一辈子都烂在这椅子上时
You're telling me you lost your mojo just in time.
你又正巧和你的能力说永别了
To get me stuck in this trap the rest of my life!
抱歉
I'm sorry.
去你妈的天使
Shove it up your ass.
至少他开始说话了
Well, at least he's talking now.
我听得见
I heard that.
时间不多 我们得谈谈
I don't have much time. We need to talk.
求之不得
Okay.
你打算杀了路西法
Your plan to kill Lucifer.
没错 你想来帮我一把吗
Yeah, you want to help.
不 蠢货 那根本没用
No. it's foolish. it can't be done.
噢 真是谢谢你的金玉良言
Oh. well, thanks for the support.
不过我已经找到了解决之道
But I believe I have the solution.
米迦勒并非唯一
There is someone besides Michael.
还有人够格与路西法抗衡
Strong enough to take on Lucifer …
甚至够格阻止天启降世
Strong enough to stop The Apocalypse.
是谁啊
Who's that.
正是将我复活又救你们到飞机上的那位
The one who resurrected me and put you on that airplane.
也正是这一切的缔造者
The one who began everything.
上帝
God.
我要找到上帝
I'm gonna find god.
[邪恶力量 第5季第2集]
- 上帝 - 没错
- God. - Yes.
- 上帝 - 是的
虽然他不在天堂 但他绝对就在某处
He isn't in heaven. he has to be somewhere.
不如去新墨西哥州找找 听说他幻化为墨西哥薄饼神了
Try New Mexico. I hear he's on a tortilla.
不 他不在那些面包片上
No, he's not on any flatbread.
听着 呆子 即使上帝真的存在
Listen, chuckles, even if there is a God,
要么早就挂了 这还是比较好听的说法
He is either dead … and that's the generous theory …
他还活着 迪恩
He is out there, Dean.
要么他就是怕得缩到一边
Or he's up and kicking.
当起了缩头乌龟
And doesn't give a rat's ass about any others.
你自己睁眼看看 如今已经大战在即了
I mean, look around you, man. the world is in the toilet.
准确地说我们就没几天能活了
We are literally at the end of days here,
而他老却还能躲在一边袖手旁观
And he's off somewhere drinking booze out of a coconut.
- 不是吗 - 够了
- All right? - Enough.
我不是来跟你讨论神学问题的
This is not a theological issue.
而是战略问题
It's strategic.
得上帝者 得胜利
With God's help, we can win.
那是白日做梦 卡西
It's a pipe dream, Cass.
这星期我已经杀了俩天使了
I killed two angels this week.
都是我的弟兄
My brothers.
我猎杀同族 成了叛变者
I'm hunted. I rebelled.
我会沦落如此 这一切 都拜你所赐
And I did it … all of it … for you.
全因你的过失所致
And you failed.
你和你老弟一手造就了这一切
You and your brother destroyed the world.
让我失去所有 换来的竟是一无所有
And I lost everything … for nothing.
所以你别在那儿义正严词地教训我
So keep your opinions to yourself.
既然你并不是来探病关怀我们的
You didn't drop in just to tear us a new hole.
那您有何贵干呢
What is it you want.
我是来借东西的
I did come for something.
护身符
An amulet.
什么护身符
What kind.
非常罕有和强大的
Very rare, very powerful.
它能感应到上帝的存在 并帮我找到他
It burns hot in god's presence. it'll help me find him.
就是说是上帝探测器
A-a god emf.
我完全搞不懂你在说些啥
Well, I don't know what you're talking about.
反正我可没那玩意儿
I got nothing like that.
我知道你没有
I know. you don't.
吓 是这个
What … this.
能借我吗
May I borrow it?
不行
No.
迪恩 借给我
Dean. give it to me.
好吧 可以借你
All right, I guess.
别搞丢了
Don't lose it.
好极了 我彻底被扒干净了
Oh, great. now I feel naked.
我会再跟你联络的
I'll be in touch.
如果找到上帝了 记得让他捎条好腿给我
When you find god, tell him to send legs!
你的皮带 用你的皮带
Your belt. your belt!
这儿 拿着
Here … hold this.
说话
Hello.
鲍比
Bobby.
鲍比 该死的 能听清楚吗
Bobby, damn it, can you hear me.
我听不清楚
I can't hear you.
听着 我需要帮助
Listen. I need a little help.
看来这次恶魔盯上我了
Seems I'm up to my ass in demons.
该死的整个镇的人都被恶魔附了身
Whole damn town's infested.
你在哪儿呢
Where are you.
通 拉多
pass rado.
科罗拉多州
Coloro… colorado.
科罗拉多州的河通镇
River pass, colorado.
河通镇
River pass!
鲁弗斯
Rufus.
你还在吗
You there.
鲁弗斯
Ruf… rufus.
鲍比 这里是
Bobby, it's …
你在那里？鲁弗斯
Are you there, ruf… rufus.
这是进出的必经之路
This is the only road in or out.
没信号
No signal.
鲁弗斯是对的 恶魔锁定了这个地方
Rufus was right. demons got this place locked down.
看来我们要徒步了
Looks like we're hiking in.
麻烦还真是络绎不绝啊
And the hits just keep on coming.
艾伦
Ellen.
孩子们好
Hello, boys.
艾伦 这里怎么回事？
Ellen, what the heck's going on here.
我们没被附身
We're us.
真高兴见到你们
Real glad to see you boys.
我真应该对你这傻子开枪
The can of whup ass I ought to open on you.
你就不能来个电话
You can't pick up a phone.
你这混蛋就不能让我安心
What are you … allergic to giving me peace of mind.
我从鲁弗斯那儿才知道你还活着
I got to find out that you're alive from rufus!
- 对不起 艾伦 - 你可好
- Sorry, ellen. - Yeah, you better be.
你最好把我弄成快速拨号 孩子
You better put me on speed dial, kid.
是的 夫人
Yes, ma'am.
这是怎么回事 艾伦
What's going on, ellen.
超出了我能独自处理的范围
More than I can handle alone.
有多少恶魔在这里
How many demons are there.
几乎整个镇
Pretty much … whole town,
除去死人和这些家伙
Minus the dead people and these guys.
这是不是到了
So this is it, right.
世界末日
End times.
肯定是
It's got to be.
差不多吧
Seems like it.
是我
It's me.
这是萨姆和迪恩
This is sam and dean.
他们是来这里帮忙的猎人
They're hunters … here to help.
你们知道这整件鬼事情
You guys hip to this whole demon thing.
恩 你呢？
Yeah. are you.
我妻子的眼睛变黑了 她拿着砖块冲向我
My wife's eyes turned black. she came at me with a brick.
有点让人拥抱超自然的感觉
Kind of makes you embrace the paranormal.
好 赶上我们了
All right, catch us up.
我怀疑我知道的比你多一点儿
I doubt I know much more than you.
鲁弗斯电话里说他正在城里调查征兆
Rufus called … said he was in town investigating omens.
整个镇突如其来的都发疯了
All of a sudden, the whole town was possessed.
我和乔在附近
Me and jo were nearby …
你和乔一起猎鬼
You're hunting with jo.
暂时的
Yeah, for a while now.
我们来到这里 这地方
We got here, and the place …
这地方就像你看到的一样
Well, the place was like you see it.
找不到鲁弗斯 然后我和乔就失散了
Couldn't find rufus. then me and jo got separated.
当我找到你们的时候我要正出去找她
I was out looking when I found you.
别担心 我们会找到她的
Don't worry. we'll find her.
不管怎样 这些人不能只坐在这儿
Either way, these people cannot just sit here.
我们现在要带他们出去
We got to get them out now.
不 那没那么容易 我曾经试过
No, it's not that easy. i've been trying.
我们已经做过一次了
We already made a run for it once.
发生了什么？本来我们有20个
What happened there used to be 20 of us.
现在有我们3个了
Well, there's three of us now.
你不知道外面是什么情况
You don't know what it's like out there.
恶魔们无处不在
Demons are everywhere.
我们不可能掩护每一个人
We won't be able to cover everybody.
要是我们每人都给枪呢
What if we get everyone guns.
你想要那边的孕妇背把枪出门当兰博
What … are you gonna arm up baby bump over here.
我们一次射击越多的盐弹 就可以避开越多的恶魔
More salt we can fire at once, more demons we can keep away.
我们经过的时候这有一个体育用品商店
There's a sporting-goods store we passed on mai.
我打赌他们有枪
I bet they got guns.
好 你留下
All right. you stay.
我们走
We'll go. what about …
如果乔和鲁弗斯在那里 我们会把他们带回来
If jo and rufus are out there, we'll bring them back.
等一下
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. hold on.
我一个人上去就够了
Why don't I just go.
你一个人吗
What alone.
总得有个人呆在这里
Well, yeah. somebody's got to stay here.
教他们使用枪支
and start to give them guns for the war.
- 艾伦会的 - 不行
- Yeah ellen. - No, no, no.
如果你留下来帮她 事情就简单多了
It's gonna go a lot faster if you stay and help, okay.
然后你就一个人带着枪和盐去找乔和鲁弗斯
While you go get guns and salt and look for jo and rufus.
大错特错
That's stupid.
我能搞定的
I can handle it.
你只是不想我出去碰到恶魔吧
You don't want me going out there.
我可没有那么说
I didn't say that.
- 靠近恶魔 - 我才没有那么说
- Around demons. - I didn't say that.
那好 我们一起去
Fine. then let's go.
我去拿盐 你去拿枪
I'll get the salt. you get the guns.
我们一起去拿盐
We'll go together.
迪恩 盐就在跟前
Dean, it's right there.
我们能专业点么
Can we at least do this like professionals.
[咒语]
萨姆
Sammy.
了解 我们再试次
Okay, roger, try again.
知道怎么用这支枪吗
You know your way around a gun at all.
在哪服过役呢
Where'd you serve.
费卢杰（伊拉克城市） 去了两次
Fallujah, two tours.
回来一年多了
Got back a little over a year ago.
拿什么会什么
Takes one to know one.
你在哪服役
Where'd you serve.
地狱
Hell.
不开玩笑
No, seriously.
当然
Seriously.
就是地狱
Hell.
怎么了
What's wrong.
刚才在超市里
Just at the store.
那些恶魔居然附体在青少年身上
Those demons were possessing teenagers.
我不得不切开这些孩子们的喉咙
I mean, i had to slit some kid's throat.
别这样 萨姆 你必须这么做
Come on, sam. you had to.
我知道 我只是
I know. I just … it used to be.
希望能像过去一样拯救这些人
I just wish I could save people, like I used to.
什么 你是说像你过去沉溺于饮用恶魔血那样
What? you mean when you were all hopped up on demon blood.
我 我不是那个意思
I-i didn't say that.
我要出去会
I'll be back.
你要去哪
Where you going.
我不想六神无主地坐在这里发呆
I can't sit here on my ass.
我女儿被困在外面某个地方
My daughter's out there somewhere.
如果半小时内我没有回来
I'm not back in half an hour, go.
带着这些人离开这里
Get these people out of here.
等等
No, wait.
我和你一起去
I'll go with you.
等等 我可以单独和你说几句吗
Whoa. hold on. can I talk to you for a second.
你又想出去吗
You're gonna go out there again.
出去干点活打发时间没什么大不了
Well, crap doesn't hit the fan with coffee breaks.
我也去
I'll go.
不用了 呆在这里让大家准备好
It's fine. Just stay here, get 'em ready.
我会照顾好艾伦的
i'll cover ellen.
为什么就你能去呢
Why's it got to be you.
我差点忘了
Oh, that's right. I forgot.
你以为我看一眼恶魔
You think i'll take one look at a demon.
就会突然忘乎所以了
And suddenly fall off the wagon,
好像经过了这么多事情
As if, after everything,
我还没有得到教训似的
i haven't learned my lesson.
难道不是吗
Well, have you.
如果你真的以为我会
If you actually think …
你最后一次看到她是在哪
So, where'd you see her last.
就在前面
Up ahead.
你和迪恩之间发生了什么事
So, what's up with you and dean.
这不难察觉
It was hard not to notice …
这些天你们兄弟到底碰到了什么诡异的事
How different things are between you guys these days.
很多糟糕的事吧
Lot of bad road there, huh.
怎么了 某个女人爱上你了还是别的
What happened? some girl come between you or something.
仅仅是工作上的压力
Just stresses of the job.
你知道是怎么回事
You know how it is.
你和乔一起猎杀恶魔 有点让人吃惊
Kind of surprised … you and jo hunting.
你不是总说她不能过这种生活吗
Weren't you always saying she couldn't hack the life.
的确不能
She can't.
但是如果她执意要这么做的话
But if she's gonna do it anyway.
你想亲自照顾她
You want to keep an eye on her.
那个烟囱是在冒烟吗
Is that a chimney going.
好像是的
Looks like it.
快来
Come on.
貌似我们找到他们的老巢了
Guess we found base camp.
恶魔不会感到寒冷
Demons don't get cold.
真奇怪 他们在烧什么
Makes you wonder what they're burning.
别动 臭娘们
Don't move, you evil skank!
别伤害她 别
Don't you hurt her. don't you …
让我妈妈回来 你这黑眼婊子
Give me my mom back, you black-eyed bitch!
艾伦 快跑
Ellen! run!
抓到你了 混蛋
Got you now, you bastard.
你是挣脱不了这个的
No way you're getting out of those.
你总算是上钩了
Did you up myself.
跟我预期的一样
You're stuck right where I want you.
你这狗娘养的恶魔
You evil son of a bitch.
不
No.
等等
W-wait, wait, wait.
Just … just wait.
停下来
Stop!
求你了
Please!
耶和华是我的牧者 我必不至缺乏
The lord is my shepherd. I shall not want.
他使我躺卧在青草地上
He layeth me down in green pastures,
他再次拯救了我
And he raiseth me up again.
我虽然行过死荫的幽谷
Yea, though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death.
也不怕遭害
I shall fear no evil.
萨姆呢
Where's sam.
它们抓了他么
They took him.
恶魔们抓住了他么
Demons took him.
上帝啊
Oh, my god.
它们在这里怎么办 那些恶魔
What if they're in here … the demons.
它们能进来么
Could they get in.
不能
No.
大家都紧张起来
Everybody sit tight.
我得去
I got to.
我们该定个计划先 把所有情况都跟我说一遍
Okay, we need to get a plan together. tell me everything.
求你了 别
Please! come on!
听着 这事有点不对
Look. something's not right.
知道么
Do you see that.
上帝啊
Geez!
有没搞错
Come on!
停下来 听我说
Stop. listen to me.
等一下
Wait a second.
- 为什么没用 - 我不知道
- Why isn't it working. - I don't know.
听我说 这事有些古怪
Look, listen to me. something's not right.
他可没自己想象的那么坚强
But he's not as strong as he thinks he is.
你能发现的
You can see that.
拜托
Please. please.
听我说
Just listen to me.
迪恩 乔也被附身了
Dean, one of them's in jo.
我们得把她安全地救出来
We got to get it out without hurting her.
它竟然叫我婊子
It called me a bitch.
你也太脆弱了吧
Bruise a little easy, don't you think.
不是 我不是那意思
No, that's not what I meant.
它叫我黑眼婊子
It called me a black-eyed bitch.
这算是哪门子恶魔
What kind of demons are these.
圣水和盐都没用
Holy water and salt roll right off.
我女儿也许是个傻子 但是她不笨啊
My daughter may be an idiot, but she's not stupid.
她带着反附身的咒语
She wears an anti-possession charm.
这有点奇怪了 对吧
It's all kind of weird, right.
所有的事都不对劲
The whole thing's off.
你觉得呢
What's your instinct.
我觉得
My instinct.
我觉得应该打给鲍比或者萨姆
My instinct is to call bobby and ask for help. or sam.
哟 那倒是麻烦了 这里就我俩
Well, tough. all you got's me, and all I got's you.
好好想想
So let's figure it out.
好
All right.
你知道鲁弗斯为什么来这个镇么
Do you know why rufus came to town.
有什么特别的预兆么
Was there a specific omen.
他有说些跟水有关的
He said something about water.
我只知道这些
That's all I know.
神父 你知道什么跟水有关的事吗
Padre, you know what she's talking about … the water.
河 河突然被污染了
The river … ran polluted all of a sudden.
什么时候
When.
上个礼拜三
Last wednesday.
第二天就有恶魔出现了
And the demon thing started up the next day.
还有有别的吗
Anything else anything.
有是有 不过挺像随机事件的
Maybe. but it's pretty random.
有随机事件是好事
Good. random's good.
流星 这算么
Shooting star … does that count.
非常大 同一晚 周三
Real big. Same night … Wednesday.
绝对算数
That definitely counts.
你认为这是外太空来的
So, uh, you think that all this comes from outer space.
这可不是《X档案》 伙计
This isn't X Files, pal.
就有烧着的大星
And there fell a great star from heaven,
好像火把从天上落下来 落在江河上
Burning like a torch, and it fell upon the river,
这星名叫“苦堇”
And the name of the star was Wormwood.
就有许多人死了
And many men died.
《启示录》八章十节
Revelation 8: 10.
你的意思是 这是天启的一部分
Are you saying that this is about the Apocalypse?
可以这么说
You could say.
这些预兆 是什么的前兆
And these specific omens … they're prelude to what?
天启四骑士
The four horsemen.
骑红马的是哪一个
And which one rides the red horse?
战争
War.
主道上停的那辆红色野马
That cherry Mustang parked on main.
你不会认为天启骑士驾的是车吧
You can't think that a car…
是我就这么干
It's the way I'd roll.
我是说 想想看
I mean, think about it.
全都对的上
It all makes sense.
如果战争化成人形来到这
If War is a dude and he's here,
或许是他在作怪
Maybe he's messing with our heads.
让我们彼此为敌
Turning us on each other.
你说乔叫你黑眼睛婊子
You said Jo called you a black-eyed bitch.
他们以为我们是恶魔 我们以为他们是恶魔
They think we're demons. We think they're demons.
如果根本没有恶魔
What if there are no demons at all.
我们是在互相残杀呢
And we're all just killing each other?
等下 慢点儿说
Wait … just back up.
这是天启
It's the Apocalypse.
很抱歉 神父
Sorry, padre.
你到底是谁
Who the hell are you?
你是什么
What are you?
猜中了 变个人形来看热闹的
You caught me. Popped in to watch.
我有这本事
I can hustle like that.
这里人人都认识的罗杰 真的罗杰哪儿去了
So, the Roger everyone around here knows … the real Roger.
埋在沟里了
Buried in a ditch.
那你是谁
So, who are you?
给个提示
Here's a hint.
我到过德国
I was in Germany.
之后又到过一次德国
Then in Germany.
再到中东
Then in the Middle East.
收到传呼的时候 我正在苏丹达尔福尔
I was in Darfur when my beeper went off.
我在等待和我的兄弟重聚
I'm waiting to hook up with my siblings.
我有三个兄弟
I've got three.
我们在一起会玩得很开心
We're gonna have so much fun together.
我知道你是谁了
I know who you are.
镇上根本就没有恶魔 是不是
There aren't any demons in town, are there?
对的
Nope.
只是恐慌的人们割了彼此的喉咙罢了
Just frightened people ripping each other's throats out.
我需要做的其实并不多
I really haven't had to do too much.
这边毁座桥
Take out a bridge here, lay in a.
那边施一点儿幻术
Little hallucination there.
坐下拿着爆米花 看好戏
Sit back, pop some corn, watch the show.
说实话 你们这些小动物真邪恶呢 萨姆
Frankly, you're really vicious little animals, Sam.
不
No.
都是你干的
You're doing this.
承认吧
Please.
上一周 这里还是世外桃源
Last week, this was Mayberry.
现在就已经到了屠戮幼童的地步
Now these people are stabbing each other's children.
因为你让他们视彼此为恶魔
'cause you made them see demons!
说句实在话 人类自相残杀是不需要理由的
Honestly, people don't need a reason to kill each other.
我是说 想想爱尔兰人
I mean, you seen the Irish.
他们不都是爱尔兰人
They're all Irish.
你认为我是个怪物
You think I'm a monster.
我不过是派对上的果冻
I'm jello shots at a party.
让人们放下禁制而已
I just remove inhibitions.
我要亲手杀了你
I'm gonna kill you myself.
那真是太好了 你可是我的代表作呢
Oh, that's adorable, considering you're my poster boy.
你什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
你自从那晚看见那刀刃上滴着的血
You can't stop thinking about it…
就一直都忘不掉
Ever since you saw it dripping off the blade of that knife.
你胡说
You're wrong.
保证留着给你哥哥听吧
Save your protests for your brother.
我能看到你心中所想
I can see inside your head.
你的欲望单纯得很呢
And, man, it is one-track city in there.
血 血 血
Blood, blood, blood.
对力量的
Lust.
贪婪
For power.
一如既往
Same as always.
你想再次强大起来
You want to be strong again.
但不是一般的强大
But not just strong.
而是强于任何人
Stronger than everybody.
愿望很美好 但你是自寻死路 小子
Good intentions … quick slide to hell, buddy boy.
我知道你现在不好过
You feel bad now.
呆会儿你就可以享用大餐了嗜血
Wait till you're thigh-deep in warm corpses.
我的朋友 好戏才刚开场呢
Because, my friend, i'm just getting started.
荤宴开始咯
Showtime for the meat suits.
好好欣赏吧
Watch this.
他下的手
He did it!
他说恶魔要来了 要来抓我们了
He said they're coming! he said they're coming to get us!
别这样 乔 鲁弗斯 他在撒谎
Stop. jo, rufus, he's lying.
你给我闭嘴
You shut your mouth.
别啊 乔 他在说谎
Please! jo! he's lying!
你是说根本没恶魔这回事
So, now you're saying that there are no demons.
是有人在作怪
And that war is a guy.
你之前可不是这么想的
You believed crazy before.
快开门 让我进去
Open up! let me in!
是我
It's me!
我发现那些恶魔了
I saw them … the demons.
他们知道我们要逃跑
They know we're trying to leave.
他们说我们谁都不可能逃脱的
They said they're gonna pick us off one by one.
等下 等下
Wait, wait, wait. what.
你刚才还说没有恶魔的呢
I thought you said there were no demons.
我只说这里没有 你去哪了
There's not. where did you go.
总得有人出去侦查吧
I thought someone should go out and see what's going on!
你在哪看见恶魔的 他们说了什么
Where did you see the demons, and what did they say exactly.
我们在这是坐以待毙
We just sit here, we're gonna be dead.
绝对不会的
No, we're not!
他们会杀死我们的 除非我们先下手为强
They're gonna kill us … unless we kill them first.
打住 打住
Okay, hold on. hold on.
不行 老兄 我们还得保护他们呢
No, man, we got people to protect.
好了 身强力壮的人跟我走 去猎魔
All right, the able-bodied go, hunt some demons.
别操之过急
Whoa, whoa, whoa. slow your roll.
整件事就和恶魔无关
This is not a demon thing.
快看他们的眼睛
Look at their eyes!
他们是恶魔
They're demons!
快走 快走
Go, go!
希望一切都是真的
Hope those are real.
他们两人说不定从一开始就被附身了
Those two could have been demons the entire time.
之前用的盐和圣水… 在我看来 全他妈是屁话
All this salt and holy-water talk … as far as i'm concerned, it's all crap.
你确定吗
Are you sure.
不是你死就是我亡
It's them or us.
我在厨房里看到有一些刀可以用
I think I saw some knives in the kitchen.
好极了
Great.
走吧
Go.
鲁弗斯
Hey, rufus.
干嘛
Yeah.
爆破筒对恶魔没有杀伤力的
Pipe bombs won't kill a demon.
没错
Right.
但在我看来
But in my experience.
如果恶魔的肉身少了腿的话
Demons come at you slower.
也就快不起来了
If they're in a body with no limbs.
可我母亲也在他们那
One of them is in my mother.
乔 听着 你知道我会竭尽全力
Jo, listen to me. you know i'm gonna do everything I can.
你妈会没事的
Your mom's gonna be okay.
只要她别从窗户进来
Unless she comes through that window.
好了 行动
All right, let's move.
低下身 脚步放慢
Stay low. move fast.
鲁弗斯
Rufus!
你给我听着 乔安娜·贝丝·哈维尔
Now, you listen up, joanna beth harvelle.
听我说 我不是恶魔
Listen to me. i'm not a demon.
好好想想 鲁弗斯 所有的征兆
Think, rufus. all those omens.
你去死吧
You go to hell.
鲁弗斯
Rufus!
被污染的水 还有那流星
The polluted water, the shooting star,
以及红马 大战开始了
The red mustang … it's war.
我告诉你 大战开始了
I'm telling you, it's war.
你说的没错
You're damn right it is.
是天启四骑士
The horseman!
天启四骑士
Horseman.
没错 他让我们倒戈相向
Yes. he's turning us against each other.
这都是你的幻觉
You're hallucinating.
天启四骑士
The horseman.
战争
War.
没错
Yes.
是你自己弄清真相的吗？大天才
Did you figure this out all by yourself, genius.
我们都搞定了吗
We all on the same page.
嗨 乔
Hi, jo.
嗨
Hey.
好吧 我们得找到战争
Okay we got to find war.
阻止小镇居民互相残杀
Before everybody in this town kills each other.
见鬼！
Damn it!
- 萨姆呢？- 在楼上
- Where's Sam? - Upstairs.
拿着
Take this.
- 好 - 你们三个从背后迂回
- All right. - You three go around back.
从小巷走
Take the alley.
迪恩 不是恶魔干的
Dean. it's not demons.
- 是天启四骑士的战争 - 没错
- It's war. - War.
我就是不明白他是怎么办到的
I just can't figure out how he's doing it.
是戒指
The ring.
戒指 没错 就是戒指
The ring. the ring … that's right.
他只要一转戒指 所有人都产生了幻觉
He turned it right before he made everybody hallucinate.
- 好像看见了恶魔 - 没错
- And go hellbitch. - Right.
我们得出去 快点
We got to move. come on.
伙计们 都停火！
People, cease fire!
停止射击！
Stop shooting!
住手！
Stop!
我真是上了年纪了
I'm getting too old for this.
不要相信你的眼睛 亲爱的
I'm not what you think, honey.
快 摁住这儿
come on, keep t.
我已经说了停火
stop firing usually means stop firing.
真是把精巧的小刀
That's a sweet little knife.
但是 有点常识好不
But come on.
你们杀不了我的 兔崽子们
You can't kill war, kiddos.
我们知道
Oh, we know.
看来 离世界末日还有一段时间
So, pit stop on mount doom.
迪恩
Dean …
萨姆 别来这套
Sam, let's not.
不 听着 这至关重要
No, listen. this is important.
我知道你不信任我
I know you don't trust me.
而我也渐渐意识到了
Just now I realize something.
连我也无法信任自己
I don't trust me either.
我一看到那鲜血
From the minute I saw that blood,
我脑海里回闪的只有那可怕的念头
Only thought in my head.
我不听说服自己 我的出发点是好的
And I tell myself it's for the right reasons,
我旨在行善
My intentions are good,
而这种感觉是千真万确的 知道吗
And it … it feels true, you know.
但是我觉得 在那表面下
But I think, underneath.
我只是忽视了什么重要的东西
i just miss the feeling.
我知道这听起来很糟糕
I know how messed up that sounds,
就如同现在 我把一切都搞砸了
Which means I know how messed up I am.
关键问题并不在于我体内的恶魔血液
Thing is, the problem's not the demon blood … not really.
我不能把我的所作所为怪罪于露比
An, what I did, i can't blame the blood or ruby.
或是其他任何人 任何事
Or anything.
这都是我自己造成的
Problem is me.
我执迷不悟
How far i'll go.
我体内的恶魔
Something in me.
让我感到恐惧不安 迪恩
scares the hell out of me, dean.
我无法再去猎魔了
I'm in no shape to be hunting.
我必须退出 因为我本身太危险
I need to step back, 'cause I'm dangerous.
也许 我们最好还是分开行动
Maybe's best we just go out spearate ways.
嗯 我觉得你说的没错
Well, i think you're right.
猜疑是最大的战斗
Suspecting a fight.
事实上 要我花费更多的精力担心你
Turth is I spent more time worried about you.
而不是怎样处理好眼下的问题
And about doing a job right.
而我做不到这样 知道吗
how just I can't for that, you know?
在现今的局势下不行
And now.
我很抱歉 迪恩
I'm sorry Dean.
这我知道 萨姆
I know you are, sam.
你…
Hey you are…
不需要车吗？
Won't taking Impala?
没关系了
It's OK.
保重 迪恩
Take care yourself, dean.
你也是 萨姆
Yeah, you too, sammy.